Anh Tran

Full-Stack Web | Mobile App Developer

PROFILE

I am a Full-stack developer with 5 years of experience in using various kinds of developing languages.

I have the ability to design/build/launch Websites and Mobile Apps from scratch till production.

I am also specialized in GIS analysis, development, and programming with full life cycle development on ESRI and opensource GIS APIs.

Plus, I am familiar with Blockchain development.

CONTACT

Email: fullstackdeveloper917@gmail.com

Home: Fairfax, VA 22031 United States

EDUCATION

George mason university 2009-2012 Associate of Science (AS), Computer science

LANGUAGE

- English Fluent
- Vietnamese Fluent
- Chinese Beginner

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer | Green Rabbit Game

February 2022 - November 2022

Green Rabbit Game is a NFT game Platform. And I worked as a front-end developer in this company.

I contributed to build beautiful, responsive websites and dashboard which interact with users directly.

I mostly worked with JS, TS and Svelte for the front-end development. and I also worked on back-end development which was Smart Contracts.

Full Stack Developer | Bell Pepper Investment

February 2020 - April 2022

Bell Pepper Investment is a real estate company. I have built several websites and platforms. The main stack I used during my stay in Bell Pepper Investment was ROR stack and React.js + Django stack. I was also involved in mobile app development, using React Native.

Spring MVC | AliExpress

March 2018 - February 2020

I have 2 years of experience with building e-commerce using Spring framework.

This is my company: https://www.aliexpress.us/

I have built some Back-end and Dashboard (Front-end) with team.

I have used some skills such as Spring MVC, JDBC, JSP and Angular.

I have also worked by using Spring boot on IntelliJ IDEA.

I have worked on git with my team and tested by using JUnit and TestNG.

Full Stack Web | Mobile App developer | Self-Employed

January 2017 - March 2018

I started my career as a developer in 2017. I mostly did web development and mobile app development for the clients which I met on freelancing platforms. I continuously try my best to get myself experts in development. I never stop learning new skills and improving the code quality. By doing this, I was able to deliver satisfying works to my clients. As I worked as freelancer, I was able to become experts in those skills: Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Tailwind, JS, TS, React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, PHP, Laravel, Django, ROR, AI, Discom and React native/Flutter for Mobile App development.

SKILLS (NOT ALL ARE LISTED:)

- 5 years of: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Json, PHP, Laravel, CodeIgniter and MySOL
- ➤ 4 years of: React.js, Node.js, Redux, Angular.js, Vue.js, Express.js, TypeScript, WordPress, Shopify, MongoDB, ArcGIS(Analysis, Mapping), Remote Sensing, Google Map/Mapbox, Geo Django (python), GDAL (Python, C++), PostGIS, OpenLayer/Cesium /Leaflet, AWS for GIS Server(S3)

- > 3 years of: React Native, PostgreSQL, Swift, Flutter, ROR, Angular, Java
- ➤ 1-3 years of: Blockchain, NFT minting, Solana, Cardona, Solidity, Svelte, Microservice such as Cortex.
- > 2 years of: Java, Spring, JSP, Spring Boot, Spring + angular, JDBC, Spring AOP, Spring ORM, Spring Remoting, Spring Java Mail
- ➤ I have familiar working with:
 - Cloud services such as cPanel, AWS, Google Cloud, and Heroku.
 - ❖ Proficient in using Git such as GitLab, GitHub or Bitbucket.
 - Task management tool such as Jira, Trello, Asana, Notion and Clickup.
 - ❖ Building API such as Rest API, Open API, or GraphQL.
 - ❖ Utilize design tool such as Figma and Adobe XD.
 - Unit Testing such as PHP Unit, Jest, or Mocha.
 - CI/CD tools like Jenkin and AWS Pipeline.